[UKA]
Dad.
Uh!
I get it.
This all scares you.
But I am not going anywhere.
I can take care of myself.
I can do more than you know.
Please don't worry anymore.
I promise I'll be fine.
Of course,
I still need you.
But I am going back on Monday.
Hachimitsu's my home.
[UKA'S DAD]
Uka.
Lift your head.
[gasps]
I apologize
for the misunderstanding.
Please, look after my daughter.
[UKA] So.
How'd I do?
Nailed it.
[UKA]
Dad.
Mom.
This is it.
This is the new world
I've found.
♪
[birds chirping]
[Uka sighs]
[UKA] I was too excited
and got here early.
Looks like I'm the first one.
Feels like I've done
this exact thing before.
Let's use this time
to rehearse.
Hi!
I'm so sorry
for worrying everyone
last week! I...
[sighs]
[UKA]
My voice cracked.
[KAI] Feels like
we've done this before.
What do you think?
Huh?
[gasps]
Oh.
Hey,
you startled me.
[KAI]
Glad you showed up.
Good morning.
[UKA]
Good morning, Miura.
Yeah!
Look who's back, baby!
[SATORU]
Kai's here, too!
We all wanted to show up early
to welcome you back
to our little family!
Oh!
Everyone?
-Let me say--
-[TAO] You don't have to
say a thing.
We already understand
how you feel, so it's fine.
[ASUMI] Ayumi already
brought us up to speed.
I just had
a lovely conversation
with your dad, Ishimori.
[UKA]
Huh?
He said
he wanted to thank everyone,
and while he would like
to come here himself,
his wife vetoed that.
She thought he'd say
something rude again.
[all laughing]
Your old man is a weirdo,
but he's not that bad!
At least, we get
a good story out of this!
[SATORU]
For real.
[TONBO]
Couldn't be me, though!
[UKA] All those fears
and anxieties I wanted to hide.
[YASUSHI]
Same, bro.
-All right, get to your seat.
-[UKA] But they accept me
-with them.
-[YUKINO] Sure thing.
SPARKLE 10 THE
SIDE OF YOU NO ONE KNOWS
[SHIRAISHI] Sweet, we're next
to each other again!
[UKA]
It's a fresh term.
Mister Abe gave us
a new seating chart.
[YASUSHI] That's hilarious.
You're stuck!
[KAI] I don't mind
not having to move.
[MARIN]
Wait. I'm next to Kai?
Aw, yeah!
[YASUSHI] Too bad
he hates your guts, Marin.
[MARIN]
Does not!
We're cool, right?
You don't hate me!
I'll bet you, like, love me!
Let's go out sometime!
Yeah?
Doesn't that sound fun?
C'mon, don't be grouchy!
[UKA]
Like that,
he's so far away again.
[ABE] Good on you,
staying late to catch up.
[UKA]
Thank you very much, sir.
♪
[door slides open]
[breathes sharply]
[UKA]
He's still here?
He sleeps a lot.
Even during class.
Maybe he doesn't get
enough at home?
He looks so pretty.
[breathes shakily]
[KAI]
Hold onto everyone.
It's all important.
So...
you'll just have
to hold onto both.
Got it?
[UKA]
Miura,
-I love you.
-[Kai gasps]
[gasps]
[breathes in sharply]
[sighs]
What time is it?
Uh.
It's 4:30.
[UKA]
Do not panic.
I don't think
I said that out loud.
[breathe shakily]
Huh?
[KAI]
Where you goin'?
[UKA]
What?
Right.
I see.
There's a new seating chart.
My bad.
[Uka breathes in sharply]
No, uh, it's not like I don't
wanna sit next to you anymore!
[breathes shakily]
[KAI]
Then do it.
No one else is here.
[exhales]
No.
I'm okay.
For now.
[UKA]
I'm not turning him down.
I want to earn my place...
and belong at his side.
[KAI]
We're doing karaoke again.
Everyone said
they want me to bring you.
That's why I was staying late.
[Uka breathes in sharply]
[KAI] You still have time
to make an appearance?
Actually.
Good news!
My curfew just
got pushed to later!
Oh?
To when?
-Till 6:00!
-Oh.
Well, good.
I'm glad you came
and woke me up when you did.
I almost flaked on 'em.
Yeah, of course.
Don't think I'd ever seen you
fall asleep there after school.
Yeah. Haven't been
to the storage room
in a little while.
Does she miss me?
Storage room, miss you?
Yeah.
I'll go tomorrow
around lunchtime.
[breathes in sharply]
I would like to go too!
Huh.
And if I said no?
But may I?
I won't be a bother.
I'll be still as a stone.
[UKA]
We've drifted a bit.
[Kai scoffs]
[KAI]
Why're you gettin' so intense?
It's okay.
[UKA]
Now, I need to get close again.
[AYUMI]
Look, there they are!
Over here, guys!
[Ayumi chuckles excitedly]
I would've skipped
the make-up class if I knew!
Then I'm glad
I held off on telling you!
'Kay, let's go!
[door slides open]
[gasps]
[all gasp]
Hm?
♪
Hi, Kojima.
What up?
Thank you.
Last week meant a lot.
No sweat.
I can't believe
you remember my name.
Wouldn't ya like to forget it?
I don't think I'll ever
be able to forget you.
-You were my bully, after all.
-Hm?
[Remi chuckles]
Crazy that
you talk to your bully
like it's no big deal,
let alone thank her.
Don't you guys even care?
Of course, we do.
But we can't tell her
how to feel about you.
We just follow her lead.
Us being cool with you
is for her to decide.
Huh.
Why don't we all
just join hands, sing a song,
and then go
live happily ever after?
It's just so sweet and corny,
I think I'm gonna throw up.
Hey, tough guy.
I see you out at night.
Someone's getting mixed up
with the wrong crowd.
-[gasps]
-[REMI] You slip out
and don't come home till late.
What are you doing?
Or...
maybe that world's
where you actually belong.
Hey.
What does that mean?
[REMI]
Oh, nothing.
Just a little concerned is all.
-Well, I'm freaked out.
-Let's go.
[Uka breathes shakily]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
Hmm.
[Tomoya chuckles]
Hmm?
Nobody creeps me out like you!
Bye, bye, miss second rate.
Yo.
That a new phone, dude?
Yeah.
Mine flew out the window.
[SATORU]
You good, man?
[KAI]
Beats me.
[YASUSHI] Dude. Mine survived
a drop from the second floor.
[SATORU]
Kai lives nine stories up.
I thought he lived in
a two-story building.
Is that not true?
[SATORU]
Not anymore.
He moved around
the end of junior high.
[KIYOSHI]
Oh.
[YASUSHI] Nice.
I'll come visit!
Don't even try.
[YASUSHI]
You jerk.
[SATORU]
He doesn't invite anyone over,
not even me.
[UKA]
One minute, he's laughing.
The next, he's lost in thought.
[breathes sharply]
His expression goes cold.
And then...
the minute I look away,
he's gone.
[panting]
[UKA]
What?
[exhales]
-[ABE] Ishimori!
-[gasps]
Is everything okay here?
Yeah.
Apparently,
some kid was sneaking around
the storage room,
so we locked it up to make sure
they couldn't get in.
I'm glad that
Miura reported the issue.
[UKA]
One step forward,
but then...
two steps back.
He talks to me, then he's gone.
After everything
we've been through, still,
I don't know him.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
It's strange.
Is he okay?
I shouldn't pry.
After all, he's the only one
who cared about that spot.
Of course, he's free to
take it away from himself.
[door slides open]
Class!
Time to get started.
-[MARIN] Where's Kai?
-[SHIRAISHI] Is he sick?
If he is, then no one told me.
I got nada, either.
He broke his streak
of actually coming in.
-[phone vibrates]
-Hold on!
What's up, Kai?
Hey!
You there?
[SHIRAISHI] What's wrong?
-Not gettin' a word.
[MARIN]
Put him on speaker, man!
Sure.
[KAI]
I'm sleeping.
For real, bro?
[all laugh]
Hope that explains things,
teach.
[ABE]
All right.
Hey. Shouldn't you be mad
he cut class for that?
Well, I wouldn't go so easy
on the rest of you.
[MIRU] What does that mean?
He gets special treatment?
[YASUSHI] It's just
'cause he's pretty, isn't it?
[ABE] You caught me.
It's pretty privilege.
-Tough luck.
-[ALL] Aw!
I've always wondered
why he gets
so sleepy every day.
Probably
'cause he's out all night.
-[MARIN] Uh?
-Yeah.
She said he was getting in
with the wrong crowd.
[KAMAKIRI] He is tough
to contact after dark.
[MIRU] Must have
some skeletons in his closet.
[TONBO]
Ya think?
-[YASUSHI] Who could say?
-All right, settle down
so I can take attendance!
You and Ayumi are
the closest ones to him.
You got any idea?
I don't.
Not a clue.
I never realized.
Outside school,
I barely know him.
[MARIN] No way.
You're always around him.
[ABE]
Okay, quiet down!
[UKA]
I don't know him either.
No one does.
♪
[KAI]
It's okay.
Oh, Miura.
-What's up?
-[Uka gasps]
[Uka gasps]
[KAI] I forgot something.
Stand guard.
Uh.
Sure.
[door banging]
Oh, come on.
I thought I told them
the lock was broken!
Ugh, whatever.
There.
Got it.
-[UKA] Hold on.
-[KAI] Huh?
[UKA] Did you find
another place to sleep?
No.
Then what happened?
[KAI]
Don't worry about it.
I just felt done.
It's too dusty in there anyway.
But, Miura...
[KAI]
What?
[UKA]
What's wrong?
Why is he distancing us?
I'm sure this spot
meant something to him.
But I made myself
part of it without asking.
Back then,
when I found the lemon soda.
Don't hunt bottles, 'kay?
There's no point.
[UKA]
Looks like I was right.
He's saying
not to come any closer.
To stay away.
[AYUMI]
What?
You're asking us
if Kai's been acting weird?
How would I know?
He seems fine to me.
But, like...
That's good.
What's up?
Is something wrong?
No.
It's nothing.
Uh.
That one, huh?
Yeah he would always say it.
[imitating Kai]
"It's nothing."
Yeah. Used to be
a catchphrase for him.
When was the one that really
shook everyone up?
In third year?
Remember that?
Yeah!
He just came in one day
with dyed hair.
Seriously.
It's nothing.
Then. He had that
same look on his face.
What "look" are
you talking about?
-Like full deadpan?
-Bingo.
[AYUMI] He hates when people
push him for answers,
so we got nothing out of him.
That sounds about right.
He can be warm
when it comes to other people,
but talking about him?
You'll be lucky if you get
anything more than
a scary glance.
[UKA]
I get it.
I've seen that face.
But...
I have managed to see
some other sides of him.
He can laugh like a kid,
then lose himself
in his thoughts,
then gives me those cold eyes.
And every now and then,
he looks like
something's troubling him.
He has a bunch of sides.
[indistinct chatter]
Uh.
Huh?
Miura?
I want to
get to know you better.
[UKA]
I'm not trying to win anything.
I don't need to know all of it.
Hmm.
Uh!
[UKA]
Right now,
I just want a hint...
of that world
he keeps to himself.
[breathes heavily]
[REMI]
Or maybe that's the world
where you actually belong.
[UKA]
What is it?
[KAI]
Don't hunt bottles.
[UKA]
Well,
too bad!
[KAI]
Third floor.
You're in room 36.
Please follow him.
Right this way, ladies.
[BOTH]
Ah!
[PATRON]
He's so hot!
You can leave it to Kai.
He's gettin' us some regulars!
Those chicks were total babes!
I should stop by.
And there's Pineapple Earrings,
right on schedule.
Quit referring to girls
by what they wear.
[STUDENT 1]
How else do ya think
I'm gonna tell them apart?
[student 1 chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
This should be the area.
[KARASAWA]
Hey, cutie.
[gasps]
You mind?
We'd like a little word.
[STUDENT 2]
Kai,
there's some girl out there
who's been snoopin' around
and asking about you.
What does she look like?
Lemme think.
She had black hair
in a medium-length bob.
-[Kai gasps]
-Seemed kinda weird,
but she claims
she goes to your school.
Oh. Looks like
Karasawa's taking care of her.
All good!
Just let your boys
handle this stuff.
-You keep working--
-[KAI] That idiot!
[KARASAWA] Go on.
Don't make this hard on us.
Now, mind explaining
what you were up to
around here?
You stalking our boy, Kai?
It's not like that!
Oh?
It's not?
But didn't you just say
you were lookin' for him?
Yes.
She fessed up easy.
Kai's lucky, isn't he?
It's unreal.
-[Karasawa chuckles softly]
-Girls freak over him.
How about you switch to me?
[FRIEND 1]
She's my type.
[KARASAWA] You know she's
just a highschooler, right?
[UKA]
I need to run.
[FRIEND 2]
Who cares?
[all laugh]
-Huh?
-Oh. Hey.
-[panting]
-[FRIEND] You good? What's up?
[Uka shudders]
-[gasps]
-[KARASAWA] Lookie here.
Caught a stalker.
Ya mind if we take her?
Let her go.
Huh?
[Karasawa chokes]
Let her go now, sir.
Okay?
Yeah.
Message received, bud!
[thuds]
[KAI]
C'mon, Ishimori!
It's time to go.
[both panting]
♪
[UKA]
I can't tell. Is he mad?
Sorry.
[Kai chuckles]
So...
since when did you decide
to become my stalker?
You're smarter than that.
Figured you would've
picked up on my signals.
Huh?
[KAI]
I wanted some space.
[UKA]
Not until you explain why.
You're stubborn, aren't you?
Though,
guess I can blame myself
for that one.
[gasps]
[KAI]
Ishimori.
Tell me how you'd describe me.
You're very responsible.
And very caring.
You're cool, kind, and strong.
[KAI]
Even if you believe that,
it's a lot to carry.
Frankly,
it's heavy.
Hm?
[exhales]
[UKA]
Also,
even though
you're going through something,
-you care.
-[Kai gasps]
♪
[groans]
[KAI]
Hey, relax.
Didn't have to look straight
into my heart like that.
[breathes shakily]
[KAI]
Self-doubting.
Anxious.
Thinks too much.
Martyr.
Honest.
Caring.
Courageous.
[UKA] He looked
straight into my heart...
and told me what he saw inside.
Now, it's my turn.
I want to see this side of him.
-[UKA] Miura? I'm stubborn.
-[Kai gasps]
Sorry,
but I'm not done!
I want to see
more of your heart.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Last night,
I learned things about him
I never knew.
♪
[UKA]
Sorry...
[UKA] Also, I made
a kinda weird declaration.
[YURU] Oh.
Morning, Kai!
[gasps]
Morning.
[whimpering]
[UKA] I feel like
I should say something to him.
-[YASUSHI] Yo, Kai!
-Hm?
Don't tell me you're working
a part time job!
My friend says
he took this yesterday.
Looks like
you're wearing a uniform,
-and it sure isn't ours.
-[gasps]
Are you with Ishimori?
[TONBO] Kai's a workin' man?
Wild!
So, why didn't you
tell any of us, huh?
I didn't realize
money was so tight.
And I assume you knew
about this part-time job
all this time?
I didn't have any idea!
[MARIN]
Well, that's an obvious lie!
What are you
and Kai to each other?
[TAO]
Back off, Marin.
-[KAI] Yeah. Caught me.
-[gasps]
I've got a part-time job now.
And maybe I should've let
somebody else know that.
[breathes heavily]
[KAI] But I have something
to take care of now,
so I'll just have
to explain later.
♪
[UKA] What are Miura
and I to each other?
I wish I could answer,
but I can't.
Who am I to him?
♪
[gasps]
Hey, Miss Stubborn.
Aren't you coming with?
But don't you...
[KAI]
Ishimori.
[breathes sharply]
Come here.
[breathes heavily]
[UKA]
Who would see this side of him?
Who would he let in?
♪
[UKA]
So...
[KAI] You can ask me
whatever you want.
All right.
And you're okay with that?
[KAI]
Yeah.
It's a good thing.
[UKA]
The more I try to learn,
the less I understand.
Ishimori?
Want some?
I would love some.
[UKA]
There's one thing I do know.
My heart is wide awake.
♪
TO BE CONTINUED